http://www.tinneys.ie/privacy-policy

PRIVACY & SECURITY POLICY
This privacy statement is provided by Tinneys Agri Spares and is for the information of visitors to our website. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. By visiting our website, you consent to the use of your information as set out in this privacy statement. We may change our privacy statement at any time. If we change our privacy statement we will post the changes on this website. Owing to the global nature of the Internet, there is a possibility that your information may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Union. By submitting your information to us you consent to these transfers. Please note that this privacy statement is subject to the terms and conditions of use of the Tinneys Agri Spares.
Use of your personal information
We receive and store some information you enter on our website. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features. We only use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, improving our online services and communicating with you.
Protecting Your Security
To ensure that your credit, debit or charge card is not being used without your consent, we will validate name, address and other personal information supplied by you against appropriate third party databases. By accepting these terms and conditions you consent to such checks being made. In performing these checks personal information provided by you may be disclosed to a registered Credit Reference Agency which may keep a record of that information. You can rest assured that this is done only to confirm your identity, that a credit check is not performed and that your credit rating will be unaffected. All information provided by you will be treated securely and strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.
Contact Us
074 91 22374
Tinney’s Agri Spares,
Leck Road, Drumnahoe,
Letterkenny, Co Donegal,
Ireland.
Product Categories:
Home >
About Us >
Contact >
Tinneys Agri Spares News >
Pages:
